

Tho Pham

Marketing & Communications Manager

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

△ Message

. . .

Tho Pham · 3rd

Marketing & Communications Manager

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info



Pullman Hotels & Resorts

People and pages related to Tho

See all

X

>



Hotel Jobs Worldwide

Page • Hospitality 569,457 followers

Follow



Hotel Job Vacancy

Page • Hospitality 250,455 followers

Follow



Hotel Jobs | JobKing.org

Page • Staffing & Recruiting 955,951 followers

Follow

Highlights

Reach out to Tho for...

Probono consulting and volunteering.

Message

About

An ambitious professional with almost 10 years experience in 360degree Marketing for B2C/B2B for luxury brands.

Activity

608 followers



Hi anh Đức, could you please share with me. Thanks so much Anh! □



Look great. Congrats David!

Tho commented



Khoi Nguyen ơi

Tho commented

See all activity

Experience

Marketing Communications Manager



Acting Marketing & Communications Manager

Pan Pacific Hanoi ul 2018 – Jun 2019 PAN PACIFIC. 1 yr Hanoi

Marketing Supervisor

Harley-Davidson of Hanoi Nov 2015 – Apr 2017 • 1 yr 6 mos Hanoi

BD Director Assistant/North Vietnam cum CRM Manager

DB Schenker

DB schenker Apr 2012 – Oct 2015

· 3 yrs 7 mos

Customer Service and Pricing desk

Education

Hanoi Foreign Trade University

Bachelor's Degree, International Economics/Business/Trade/Commerce 2005 – 2009

Skill	اد کا	R۶	enc	ors	ρm	ent	c

Logistics Management . 11



Endorsed by Song Huynh (Open for Opportunity) and 1 other who is highly skilled at this

Pricing . 5

John Nguyen SIOR, CPM and 4 connections have given endorsements for this skill

Customer Service . 3

Mark Mustradi and 2 connections have given endorsements for this skill

Industry Knowledge

Operations Management . 2

Freight Forwarding . 2

International Trade . 1

Brand Management

PR

Strategic Communications

Digital Marketing

Interpersonal Skills

Negotiation . 2

Show less ^

Accomplishments

Languages

English • Japanese • Vietnamese

Interests

DB Schenker

179,980 followers



Accor



03,315 followers

Alaska Pacific University

3,667 followers



Nhà hàng Khách sạn Việt Nam



648 members

The Logistics of Logistics

121,671 members

Marketing Communication

Marketing 1,310,417 members

See all

People also viewed



Trung Nguyễn Trần •3rd

Digital Marketing Manager at Legacy Yen Tu - MGallery

Connect



Vinh Hạnh •3rd

Marketing And Public Relations Specialist at Mường Thanh Hospitality Corporation

Connect



Duangkamon Alex Sasirot •3rd

Marketing Communication Manager at JW Marriott Hotel Bangkok

Connect

Dac Lam •3rd

Marketing Communications Manager at Sofitel Saigon Plaza

Connect



Bill Bensley •3rd

CREATIVE DIRECTOR at BENSLEY

Connect

∨Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer							
Connect							
Nhi Duong							
Student at Ton Duc Thang University							
Connect							
→Show more							
in LEARNING							
Add new skills with these courses							
Advertising on Instagram							
10,151 viewers							
Content Marketing: How to Podcast							
33,764 viewers							
Introduction to Social Media Strategy							
11,068 viewers							
Show more on LinkedIn Learning							



inkedIn Corporation © 2021	
(Arabic) العربية	
elect Language	
Manage your account and privacy to to your Settings.	
Questions? Tisit our Help Center.	
afety Center	
mall Business	
Mobile Control of the	
ales Solutions	
dvertising	
d Choices	
Privacy & Terms >	
Marketing Solutions	
areers	
Community Guidelines	
alent Solutions	
accessibility	
bout	

